DREW GURLEY

CEO · DIRECTOR · SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER · BUSINESS ANALYST · ENTERPRISE SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT · VENTURE CAPITALIST · FOUNDER

(513) 402-2345 • Harrison, OH 45030

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over twenty years of experience in the technology sector including software engineering, project and program management, data management, development operations, systems architecture and senior-level management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

drew@evervest.group

CEO · FOUNDER · VENTURE CAPITALIST 2021 - PRESENT | THE EVERVEST GROUP LLC

The Evervest Group is an American investment firm specializing in private equity investments within the real-estate industry.

Successfully financed, renovated and closed two investment properties in the initial year of operation, grossing over a half-million dollars in first-year revenue.

DIRECTOR · SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER · ARCHITECT

2018 - PRESENT | ESOFT PLANNER LLC

PROFICIENCIES

drew.evervest.group

React, Redux, Node, Sails,
Python, Django, Django Rest
Framework, PHP, Symfony,
Zend, Laravel, PostgreSQL,
MySQL, NoSQL, Firestore,
Aurora, Aurora Serverless,
AWS, Firebase, Docker,
Vagrant, Software-as-aService, Visual Studio Code,
Git, Gitlab, SourceTree,
Webpack, Rollup, Vite,
Material UI, Styled
Components, Tailwind, Jira,
Confluence, Scrum, Kanban,

Esoft Planner is a multinational software development company providing an all-in-one software-as-a-service solution for sports facility management and resource scheduling.

Led international and domestic teams in the design, development and deployment of a next-generation, omni-vertical scheduling and resource management software.

Drafted and deployed an enterprise-wide redesign of the Operations Infrastructure and Change Management Processes. Resulted in a significant reduction of department overhead and a substantial boost to overall infrastructure reliability.

DIRECTOR · SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER · ARCHITECT

2015 - 2018 | DATA ROLE INC

Data Role Inc is a national financial technology firm providing accumulation, analysis and distribution of property centric data for real estate, insurance and financial industries.

Designed, developed and deployed a national ETL solution for the consumption,

- normalization and aggregation of data across thousands of dissonant data sources of varied mediums.
- Managed the research, scoping and implementation of a vector-based artificial intelligence algorithm for the categorization of disparate permit data.

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER · ARCHITECT 2011 - 2015 | MFM SOFTWARE INC

MFM Software Inc is a regional technology firm providing hosting, data management, IDX search and broker services

BDD, DDD, TDD, Pytest,
PhpUnit, SuperTest, Jest,
Mocha, Chai, Project
Management, Program
Management, Leadership
and Personnel Management,
Professional Development,
Business Analysis,
Budgeting, Forcasting &
Modeling

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology - University of Phoenix - March 2009

BIOGRAPHY

Drew Gurley is the CEO and Founding Member of The Evervest Group, and possesses over twenty years of experience in the technology sector.

Drew specializes in business analysis, business process optimization, enterprise solutions architecture and software engineering.

Drew is a powerful force in the workplace and uses his positive attitude and tireless energy to encourage others to work hard and succeed. to the real-estate industry.

Designed and implemented a cohesive property search engine that handles millions of requests from hundreds of thousands daily visitors.

Designed, developed and deployed an ETL solution for the consumption, normalization and aggregation of MLS and third-party property data into a vendor-facing REST API.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2008 - 2011 | MODERN MEDIA AND IT LLC

Modern Media and IT is a technology solutions firm specializing in small-business partnerships.

Collaborated with clients to design and develop numerous intellectual properties for the financial, medical, education, entertainment and e-commerce industries.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2004 - 2008 | XPERIANZ LLC

Xperianz LLC is a multinational staffing firm providing guidance and staff augmentation for the finance, business and technology sectors.

Produced BPO solutions for communication, sales management, performance record keeping, client billing, contract management and reporting.